<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[SYR] Naga (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.SYRNaga</packageId>
  <author>Syrchalis</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/SYRNaga</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
      <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/erdelf/AlienRaces/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/WAEzk68.png[/img]
Update of Syrchaliss mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1539971494

[img]https://i.imgur.com/7Gzt3Rg.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/SYRNaga][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NOW7jU1.png[/img]
[h3][b]Adds a playable naga race[/b][/h3]

[i]If you are having issues with the food AI of Naga, enable "use standard AI" in the settings[/i]

[b]Requires [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=839005762]Humanoid Alien Framework[/url] loaded before this[/b]
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1461790308]Harvest Yield Patch[/url] is not required, but highly recommended, otherwise some aspects of the race won't work as I intended them to.
    
The Naga are a technologically advanced race without a functional goverment or law enforcement since their homeworld has become inhabitable.  This means they can be found mostly on space stations and ships and occassionally on Rimworlds as well.

They tend to work as mercenaries for the highest bidder and offer their superior skills with guns. Not just as excellent shooters, but also as weapon manufacturers. Their plasma technology is only rivaled by the charge weapons of glitterworlds. Naga are also known for their regenerative abilities and proficiency at disassembling mechanoids.

Despite this their way of life does not go well with others and thus they struggle to find allies among other races.

They have advanced versions of weapons and shield belts - the shield emitter belt (see GIF) is a better smokepop belt for example.

[b]Advantages:[/b][list]
[*]Small chance to get higher quality when crafting/building/sculpting
[*]Can craft plasma versions of normal weapons (improved armor penetration, slightly better stats otherwise, require jade however)
[*]Venomous melee
[*]Heal 50% faster and have slightly better immunity gain
[*]Resistant to toxins
[*]10% faster than humans
[*]20% faster aiming
[*]20% higher psychic sensitivity
[*]20% faster entropy recovery
[*]50% more materials from disassembling mechanoids
[*]10% more meat from butchering
[/list]

[b]Disadvantages:[/b][list]
[*]20% lower overall health
[*]Low pain threshold
[*]Weak melee
[*]20% slower with plants
[*]Severely reduced plant harvest yield at low plant levels (slowly catch up to humans at higher skill)
[*]20% less animal tame chance and train chance
[*]20% less animal products
[*]Only worth 2 royal favor as gift
[*]Vulnerable to the cold
[*]Vulnerable to psychic phenomena due to their naturally higher psychic sensitivity
[*]Require special diet (anything with vegetables gives less nutrition - lavish meals, survival meals and pemmican will always work normally, ignoring ingredients)
[*]Humans dislike Naga (relation penalty)
[*]Cannot wear pants (obviously)[/list]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2024059141]Crossover[/url]
This mod will allow you to have mixed colonies or tribes with all my race mods. It comes with two scenarios as well.


__________


Also check out my other Rimworld mods:
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=1474000866]Syrchalis' Mods[/url]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Rs6T6cr.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]

</description>
</ModMetaData>
